joberr.com 2019-05-01

# Privacy Policy - Joberr

Please read this policy carefully. If you do not agree with our policies, you choose not to use Joberr.com ("Site"). By accessing or using this Site, you agree completely to this privacy policy. We reserve the right to change this policy at any time, so please check back frequently as your continued use of this site equates to you accepting this policy.

###  COPPA – Under age 13

Our Website is not intended for children under 13 years of age. Anyone under the age of 13 are not permitted to provide any personal information to or on the Site. We do not knowingly collect personal information from children under 13. If you are under 13, you are not permitted to use or provide any information on this Website, its features, make any purchases through the Site, use any of the interactive or public comment features of this Site or provide any information about yourself to us, including your name, address, telephone number, e-mail address or any screen name or user name you may use. If we discover that we have collected or received personal information from a child that is under the age of 13 without verification of parental consent, we will delete that information. If you believe we might have any information from or about a child under 13, please contact us at info@joberr.com

We recognize that your privacy is important.  This document outlines the types of personal information we receive and may collect when you use joberr.com, as well as some of the steps we take to safeguard information.  We hope this will help you make an informed decision about using joberr.com and whether to share personal information with us. This privacy statement applies to the joberr.com website (the “Website” or “Site”) and the products and services that are located in the joberr.com domain.

joberr.com strives to maintain the highest standards of decency, fairness and integrity in all our operations.

##  Personal Information

Joberr.com collects personally identifiable information from the visitors to our website only on a voluntary basis.  Personal information collected on a voluntary basis may include name and email address currently (this list of personal information may increase in the future for the purpose of running sweepstakes and contests, but if it does, changes will be noted in this section).

This information is collected if you sign up for an account at joberr.com and become a member of the Website (the ways joberr.com collects personal information may increase in the future and when this happens, changes will be made accordingly to this section).  The information collected is used for the operation of the Website, to contact members (see next section, “ **Emails sent to Members** ” below) and respond to visitor inquiries.

It should me noted that if you wish, you may choose to remain anonymous during every interaction on and with joberr.com.  There’s no obligation to share any of your personal information, beyond your email address, to fully operate the website as either the Seller or Buyer of Jobs.

If we make material changes in the collection of personally identifiable information we will inform you by placing a notice on our site and making the necessary changes to this document.

##  Emails sent to Members

Joberr.com may choose to contact its members via email for 2 very specific reasons:

1\. Notification mailings sent out to both Buyers and Sellers; a few instances of these are when a new account is opened, when someone wants to buy your Job, when the Job is entirely complete and a notice is sent out asking for feedback.

2\. Newsletters, promotional mailings and the like.

The notification mailings are absolutely necessary for the site to function properly.  These will consist only of reporting to members that either an action is required from them or a notification of some kind directly related to the operation of joberr.com.  There will be no “opt-out” to these mailings as if you are actively engaged in using joberr.com, these mailings are deemed absolutely necessary.  Moreover, if you’ve ceased your use of joberr.com or don’t have active Jobs and aren’t purchasing Jobs on the Website, there will be nothing to notify you about and you won’t receive any of these notification mailings.

As the newsletters and promotional mailings are not deemed absolutely necessary, there will be an option to “Unsubscribe” of further communications from joberr.com at the bottom of every email.  While the newsletters and any promotional mailings joberr.com sends out will be deemed beneficial by the owner and operator of joberr.com, there is an understanding that a member may wish not to receive such mailings.  While these mailings may not be exclusively related to joberr.com, the majority of said emails will be Website related and deemed beneficial by joberr.com ownership.

##  Promotions

Joberr will run periodic promotions.  Although this Privacy Policy will at all times remain valid, there will be additional Terms for any and all Promotions held on joberr.

Some promotions on the Site will be opt-in promotions where others may be set up to include all members of joberr in one way or another.  Many will necessitate some interaction with the website to be entered into the contest.  All of these scenarios will be explained in detail for each individual promotion in the Promotion section of the joberr Blog. 

Included in the Promotion section is a Promotion Guidelines document that will be valid for each Promotion and will be edited when necessary.  If this document is altered, the Revision Date will be updated and any and all changes will be made clear within that document. 

##  Use of Cookies and Web Beacons

We may use cookies to help you personalize your online experience.  Cookies are identifiers that are transferred to your computer’s hard drive through your Web browser to enable our systems to recognize your browser.  The purpose of a cookie is to tell the Web server that you have returned to a specific page.  For example, if you personalize the sites pages, or register with any of our site’s services, a cookie enables joberr.com to recall your specific information on subsequent visits.

You have the ability to accept or decline cookies by modifying your Web browser; however, if you choose to decline cookies, you may not be able to fully experience the interactive features of the site.

A web beacon is a transparent image file used to monitor your journey around a single website or collection of sites.  They are also referred to as web bugs and are commonly used by sites that hire third-party services to monitor traffic.  They may be used in association with cookies to understand how visitors interact with the pages and content on the pages of a web site.

Browsers can be set to accept or reject cookies or notify you when a cookie is being sent.  Privacy software can be used to override web beacons.  Taking either of these actions shouldn’t cause a problem with our site, should you so choose.

##  Non-Personal Information

In some cases, we may collect information about you that is not personally identifiable.  We use this information, which does not identify individual users, to analyze trends, to administer the site, to track users’ movements around the site and to gather demographic information about our user base as a whole.

##  Release of Information

If joberr.com is sold, the information we have obtained from you through your voluntary participation in our site may transfer to the new owner as a part of the sale in order that the service being provided to you may continue. 

##  How You Can Correct or Remove Information

We provide this privacy policy as a statement to you of our commitment to protect your personal information.  If you have submitted personal information through our website and would like to update or correct that information, please login to Joberr.com and make those changes via the “Settings” page in your “Profile”.  If you have submitted personal information through our website and would like that information deleted from our records, please use our “Contact Us” page and note “Cancellation” in the Subject line.

##  Updates and Effective Date

Joberr.com reserves the right to make changes to this policy.  Changes to this privacy policy are effective as of the stated "Last Update" and your continued use of the Site on or after the Last Update date will constitute acceptance of the privacy policy. We encourage you to periodically review this policy so that you will know what information we collect and how we use it.

##  Agreeing to Terms

If you do not agree to the joberr.com Privacy Policy as posted here on this website, please do not use this site or any services offered by this site.

Your use of this site indicates acceptance of this privacy policy.

###  Got any Questions?

If you have any questions (or comments) concerning this Privacy Policy, please email us at info@joberr.com, and we will make an effort to reply within a reasonable timeframe.
